jewelrymax.net 2018-01-27

# 

                        ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT
Jewelrymax, (Jewelrymax), is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those
individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential,
secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with
Jewelrymax of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most
existing privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Jewelrymax , and thus it shall govern any and
all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of Jewelrymax you are herein consenting to the
following data procedures expressed within this agreement.
    Collection of Information
    This website collects various types of information, such as:
    • Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing
         and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services
         and to deliver the services you have requested.
    Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and
    willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this
    site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses
    specifically provided on this site.
    It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any
    website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites
    garner, make use of and share information collected.
    Use of Information Collected
    Jewelrymax may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our
    website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary
    to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products
    and/or services that may be available to you from Jewelrymax . Jewelrymax may also be in contact with
    you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current
    or potential future services that may be offered.
    Jewelrymax does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or
    names to any third parties.
    Jewelrymax may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do
    so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary
    or is required in an effort to:
    • Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any
         process which may be served upon Jewelrymax and/or our website;
    • Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Jewelrymax; and

• Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of
    Jewelrymax and/or the general public.
Children Under Age of 13
Jewelrymax does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of
thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been
inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the
necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the
age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us
and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To
discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to
Kayz@jewelrymax.net. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must
go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Jewelrymax does not claim nor accept
responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore,
we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy
statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The
aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our
website.
Security
Jewelrymax shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural
and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any
loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under
our control.
The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an
effort to build users' trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure
access and communication of credit card and personal information.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
Jewelrymax reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we
will post those change to our website homepage at Jewelrymax, so that our users and/or visitors are
always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances,
if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Jewelrymax decides to make use of
any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated
when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email.
Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this
separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the
aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions,
then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website

following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in
agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website,
please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: support@jewelrymax.net
Telephone Number: 714-988-0330
Mailing Address:
    Jewelrymax
    1300 Pioneer Street
    Brea, California 92821
